{"classes":["PERSON_NAME","ADDRESS","EDUCATION","GPA","SKILL","EXPERIENCE_LEVEL","JOB_TITLE","DATE_BIRTH","MAJOR","MARIAGE_STATUS","ORGANIZATION","GENDER","LOCATION"],"annotations":[["Bang cap cao nhat Cu nhan Trinh do ngoai ngu Vietnamese Ban ngu English Trung cap Cong viec gan day nhat Technical Manager Cong ty gan day nhat Global Outsource Solution GOS Cap bac hien tai Truong phong Muc Tieu Nghe Nghiep CTO / Managing Director / Country Manager/ Operations Manager for web agency / outsourcing / dotcom online company Thanh Tich Noi Bat Expert in web development especially in social networking portal e commerce listing services jobs real estate classified... using LAMP Linux Apache mySQL PHP or LNMP Linux Nginx mySQL PHP More than 10 years in web outsourcing for Euro market I have been working for famous outsourcing agency in Vietnam like Sutrixmedia Dirox Vytech Global Outsourcing Services and have done many projects for their clients in Euro and Australia like BusinessLab RedAnt Reactive Play House Digital Cellfish Media More than 5 years in online industry with ecommerce and job listing portal I've been working for Vietnamworks.com FPT Online Hotdeal.vn Having Project Management Certification issued by Brainbench.com and Scrum Master Accredited Certification issued by scrum institute.org see at http //dreamtechjsc.com/vinhnguyen/scrum.jpg or check at http //www.scrum institute.org/International_Scrum_Institute_Certificate_Validation_Tool.php Having exprience in using caching system for high load website portal APC memcached... Expert in Ecommerce development and operations using Opencart Magento Having experience with Python language Django Scrapy Having experience with NodeJS / Express / MonggDB.. Having experience in mobile development for iPhone iPad iOS and Android Having experience in setup company / technical team recruite team build working process... and having good relationship in IT domains Hoc Van & Bang Cap Cu nhan Dai hoc Khoa Hoc Tu Nhien Tp Ho Chi Minh IT Software Thang 9/1999 Thang 2/2004 HCMC University of Natural Science HCMC VietNam Bachelor of Information Technology HCMC University of Technology HCMC VietNam Intermediate 05 2000 IT technician Vocational guideance and training Dist.",{"entities":[[18,25,"EDUCATION"],[105,122,"JOB_TITLE"],[144,173,"ORGANIZATION"],[225,228,"JOB_TITLE"],[231,248,"JOB_TITLE"],[251,267,"JOB_TITLE"],[268,286,"JOB_TITLE"],[399,416,"SKILL"],[424,434,"SKILL"],[489,493,"SKILL"],[494,499,"SKILL"],[500,506,"SKILL"],[507,512,"SKILL"],[513,516,"SKILL"],[520,524,"SKILL"],[525,530,"SKILL"],[531,536,"SKILL"],[537,542,"SKILL"],[543,546,"SKILL"],[557,565,"EXPERIENCE_LEVEL"],[667,678,"ORGANIZATION"],[679,684,"ORGANIZATION"],[685,691,"ORGANIZATION"],[793,804,"ORGANIZATION"],[805,811,"ORGANIZATION"],[855,872,"EXPERIENCE_LEVEL"],[969,972,"ORGANIZATION"],[998,1016,"SKILL"],[1060,1065,"SKILL"],[1465,1471,"SKILL"],[1481,1487,"SKILL"],[1488,1494,"SKILL"],[1518,1524,"SKILL"],[1527,1534,"SKILL"],[1537,1546,"SKILL"],[1591,1597,"SKILL"],[1598,1602,"SKILL"],[1603,1606,"SKILL"],[1611,1618,"SKILL"],[1640,1653,"SKILL"],[1772,1779,"EDUCATION"],[1780,1820,"ORGANIZATION"],[1821,1832,"MAJOR"],[1864,1898,"ORGANIZATION"],[1907,1915,"EDUCATION"],[1919,1941,"MAJOR"],[1947,1976,"ORGANIZATION"]]}]]}