{"classes":["PERSON_NAME","ADDRESS","EDUCATION","GPA","SKILL","EXPERIENCE_LEVEL","JOB_TITLE","DATE_BIRTH","MAJOR","MARIAGE_STATUS","ORGANIZATION","GENDER","LOCATION"],"annotations":[["1st / Graphic design HCM Vietnam Graphic design 2003 Brainbench HTML 3.2 Certification Brainbench Struts 1.2.x Certification Brainbench ASP.NET Certification Brainbench Master PHP5 Certification Brainbench Project Management 2005 Scrum Master issued by Scrum Institute Kinh Nghiem Lam Viec Chief Technology Officer CTO IT Phan mem Dreamtech JSC Thang 2/2010 Thang 4/2012 Duties and Achievements Operation & recruite all technical team for DreamtechJSC Web Mobile SEO UI/UX 10+ team members inlcuding Project Manager Developers and Designers Manage all technical activities of DreamtechJSC including coding and system / IT system infastructure.",{"entities":[[6,20,"SKILL"],[33,47,"SKILL"],[53,63,"ORGANIZATION"],[64,68,"SKILL"],[87,97,"ORGANIZATION"],[125,135,"ORGANIZATION"],[136,143,"SKILL"],[176,180,"SKILL"],[206,224,"SKILL"],[230,235,"SKILL"],[290,314,"JOB_TITLE"],[315,318,"JOB_TITLE"],[331,344,"ORGANIZATION"],[439,451,"ORGANIZATION"],[463,466,"SKILL"],[467,472,"SKILL"],[500,515,"JOB_TITLE"],[516,526,"JOB_TITLE"],[531,540,"JOB_TITLE"],[576,588,"ORGANIZATION"],[599,605,"SKILL"]]}]]}