{"classes":["PERSON_NAME","ADDRESS","EDUCATION","GPA","SKILL","EXPERIENCE_LEVEL","JOB_TITLE","DATE_BIRTH","MAJOR","MARIAGE_STATUS","ORGANIZATION","GENDER","LOCATION"],"annotations":[["DreamtechJSC has servers on Viettel / Netnam data center which are virtualized into VPS using HyperVM and Citrix and 2 Droplets on DigitalOcean Cloud.",{"entities":[[0,12,"ORGANIZATION"],[28,35,"ORGANIZATION"],[38,56,"ORGANIZATION"]]}],["DreamtechJSC has servers on Viettel / Netnam data center which are virtualized into VPS using HyperVM and Citrix and 2 Droplets on DigitalOcean Cloud.",{"entities":[[0,12,"ORGANIZATION"],[28,35,"ORGANIZATION"],[38,56,"ORGANIZATION"],[131,143,"ORGANIZATION"]]}],["DreamtechJSC has servers on Viettel / Netnam data center which are virtualized into VPS using HyperVM and Citrix and 2 Droplets on DigitalOcean Cloud.",{"entities":[[0,12,"ORGANIZATION"],[28,35,"ORGANIZATION"],[38,56,"ORGANIZATION"],[84,87,"SKILL"],[94,101,"SKILL"],[131,143,"ORGANIZATION"]]}],["DreamtechJSC has servers on Viettel / Netnam data center which are virtualized into VPS using HyperVM and Citrix and 2 Droplets on DigitalOcean Cloud.",{"entities":[[0,12,"ORGANIZATION"],[28,35,"ORGANIZATION"],[38,56,"ORGANIZATION"],[131,143,"ORGANIZATION"]]}]]}