{"classes":["PERSON_NAME","ADDRESS","EDUCATION","GPA","SKILL","EXPERIENCE_LEVEL","JOB_TITLE","DATE_BIRTH","MAJOR","MARIAGE_STATUS","ORGANIZATION","GENDER","LOCATION"],"annotations":[["We are also outsourced for many big companies in France and Canada like Cellfish Media SFR... Company size about 40 staffs Senior/ Team Leader IT Phan mem Sutrixmedia Vietnam Thang 6/2005 Thang 12/2006 Company Type 100% foreign invested Duties & Achievements Coding web application outsource for sutrixmedia's client and partner oversea France Business Lab www.business lab.com Australia Red Ant www.redant.com.au USA Japan PEK www.pekinteractive.com Programming web applications using HTML/Javascript PHP ASP JSP/Servlet/JavaBean.",{"entities":[[49,55,"LOCATION"],[60,66,"LOCATION"],[72,86,"ORGANIZATION"],[87,90,"ORGANIZATION"],[131,142,"JOB_TITLE"],[259,265,"SKILL"],[337,343,"LOCATION"],[344,356,"ORGANIZATION"],[378,387,"LOCATION"],[388,395,"ORGANIZATION"],[414,417,"LOCATION"],[418,423,"LOCATION"],[424,427,"ORGANIZATION"],[451,462,"SKILL"],[486,501,"SKILL"],[502,505,"SKILL"],[506,509,"SKILL"],[510,530,"SKILL"]]}]]}