{"classes":["PERSON_NAME","ADDRESS","EDUCATION","GPA","SKILL","EXPERIENCE_LEVEL","JOB_TITLE","DATE_BIRTH","MAJOR","MARIAGE_STATUS","ORGANIZATION","GENDER","LOCATION"],"annotations":[["UYEN NGUYEN NIKKINP09@HOTMAIL.COM +84 902 632 146 linkedin.com/pub/nikki nguyen/72/173/47/ EDUCATION GCE O Level 2007 2009 Diploma & Higher Diploma in Business Accounting University of Cambridge TMC Academy & Bachelor of Commerce Accounting University of Newcastle PSB Academy 2010 2013 Singapore College of Insurance M5 M9 M9A HI 2013 EXPERIENCE Wild Honey Dining & Wine Cashier/Barista 2010 2011 Singapore Bates CHI & Partners Intern Account Executive 2014 Vietnam StudioDAG Account manager 2015 Vietnam ACCOMPLISHMENT Awarded Best in Class for Business Approach to Social Etiquette Awarded Face of the month for consistently assigning to and trusting with high profile clientele ABOUT ME A Vietnamese who born in 1989.",{"entities":[[0,11,"PERSON_NAME"],[151,170,"MAJOR"],[171,206,"ORGANIZATION"],[209,217,"EDUCATION"],[221,240,"MAJOR"],[241,276,"ORGANIZATION"],[287,317,"ORGANIZATION"],[347,387,"ORGANIZATION"],[398,428,"ORGANIZATION"],[429,453,"JOB_TITLE"],[467,476,"ORGANIZATION"],[477,492,"JOB_TITLE"],[716,720,"DATE_BIRTH"]]}]]}