{"classes":["PERSON_NAME","ADDRESS","EDUCATION","GPA","SKILL","EXPERIENCE_LEVEL","JOB_TITLE","DATE_BIRTH","MAJOR","MARIAGE_STATUS","ORGANIZATION","GENDER","LOCATION"],"annotations":[["Page 1 / 2 PERSONAL INFORMATION Le Hung Cuong 63/18/11 HT45 street Hiep Thanh Ward 12 Distric 0964811059 Lehungcuong.z90@gmail.com Skype Cuong_le_nd_90 Sex Male Date of birth 28/01/1990 Nationality Kinh WORK EXPERIENCE EDUCATION AND TRAINING PERSONAL SKILLS JOB APPLIED FOR POSITION PREFERRED JOB STUDIES APPLIED FOR Quality Assurance QC PQA 2011 2012 Fresher .Net Developer at FPT Software HN service contract Training WPF HTML5 at company Develop VAIO Care on Window 8 Create testcase for VAIO Care application on Window 8 2012 2013 .Net developer at FPT Software HN QC Engineer at FPT Software HN Research and develop some app for Microsoft apply on Window 8 Preview and WinPhone 7.5 Had 4 months experience in QC Engineer Write Testcase test plan Unit Test Intergration test System Test 2013 2015 Quality Assurance QC PQA at FPT Software HN HCM Implement quality assurance process.",{"entities":[[32,45,"PERSON_NAME"],[46,93,"ADDRESS"],[156,160,"GENDER"],[175,185,"DATE_BIRTH"],[317,334,"JOB_TITLE"],[335,337,"SKILL"],[338,341,"SKILL"],[352,374,"JOB_TITLE"],[378,393,"ORGANIZATION"],[411,419,"SKILL"],[420,423,"SKILL"],[424,429,"SKILL"],[449,458,"ORGANIZATION"],[462,468,"SKILL"],[471,486,"SKILL"],[491,500,"ORGANIZATION"],[535,549,"JOB_TITLE"],[553,568,"ORGANIZATION"],[569,580,"JOB_TITLE"],[584,599,"ORGANIZATION"],[600,620,"SKILL"],[653,661,"SKILL"],[674,682,"SKILL"],[691,710,"EXPERIENCE_LEVEL"],[714,725,"JOB_TITLE"],[732,740,"SKILL"],[741,750,"SKILL"],[751,760,"SKILL"],[761,778,"SKILL"],[779,790,"SKILL"],[801,825,"JOB_TITLE"],[829,848,"ORGANIZATION"],[849,884,"SKILL"]]}]]}