{"classes":["PERSON_NAME","ADDRESS","EDUCATION","GPA","SKILL","EXPERIENCE_LEVEL","JOB_TITLE","DATE_BIRTH","MAJOR","MARIAGE_STATUS","ORGANIZATION","GENDER","LOCATION"],"annotations":[["CURRICULUM VITAE PERSONAL INFORMATIONS Full Name HO NHAT VINH Date of Birth 20 Jan 1983 Gender Male Nationality Viet Nam Marital status Married Phone 0907 140 617 Email hnvinh@gmail.com EDUCATION 2007 Ho Chi Minh University of Natural Sciences Bachelor degree of Computer Sciences 2010 Soft Skills in Project Managements Project Management Foundation PMF CAREER SUMMARY May 2012 to Present Petechim JSC Group Manager Mar 2009 to May 2012 FPT Software Project Manager Jul 2008 to Feb 2009 FPT Software Project Team Leader Mar 2007 to Jun 2008 FPT Software Developer Management skills Planning and monitoring project.",{"entities":[[49,61,"PERSON_NAME"],[76,87,"DATE_BIRTH"],[95,99,"GENDER"],[112,120,"LOCATION"],[136,143,"MARIAGE_STATUS"],[201,243,"ORGANIZATION"],[244,252,"EDUCATION"],[263,280,"MAJOR"],[301,320,"SKILL"],[321,350,"SKILL"],[351,354,"SKILL"],[390,408,"ORGANIZATION"],[409,416,"JOB_TITLE"],[438,450,"ORGANIZATION"],[451,466,"JOB_TITLE"],[488,500,"ORGANIZATION"],[501,520,"JOB_TITLE"],[542,554,"ORGANIZATION"],[555,575,"JOB_TITLE"],[583,591,"SKILL"],[596,614,"SKILL"]]}]]}