{"classes":["PERSON_NAME","ADDRESS","EDUCATION","GPA","SKILL","EXPERIENCE_LEVEL","JOB_TITLE","DATE_BIRTH","MAJOR","MARIAGE_STATUS","ORGANIZATION","GENDER","LOCATION"],"annotations":[["Hobbies a Playing Chess a Solving Rubik's Cube a Watching Series Languages a English a Hindi a Marathi Education Details January 2014 to January 2017 Bachelora s Degree Information Technology First Class Pune Maharashtra JSPMa s Jayawantrao Sawant College of Engineering January 2010 to January 2014 Diploma Information Technology First Class Nashik Maharashtra K. K. Wagh Polytechnic January 2010 SSC First Class Nashik Maharashtra New Era English School Blockchain Developer Blockchain Developer Corpcloud Global Services Pvt.",{"entities":[[10,23,"SKILL"],[26,39,"SKILL"],[77,84,"SKILL"],[87,92,"SKILL"],[95,102,"SKILL"],[150,159,"EDUCATION"],[169,191,"MAJOR"],[204,220,"LOCATION"],[221,270,"ORGANIZATION"],[308,330,"MAJOR"],[343,361,"LOCATION"],[362,384,"ORGANIZATION"],[414,432,"LOCATION"],[433,455,"ORGANIZATION"],[456,476,"JOB_TITLE"],[477,497,"JOB_TITLE"],[498,523,"ORGANIZATION"]]}]]}