{"classes":["PERSON_NAME","ADDRESS","EDUCATION","GPA","SKILL","EXPERIENCE_LEVEL","JOB_TITLE","DATE_BIRTH","MAJOR","MARIAGE_STATUS","ORGANIZATION","GENDER","LOCATION"],"annotations":[["EDUCATION & STRAINING Bachelor of Computer and Network Security 2012 AeU College of Computer of Science 2010 InfoWorld School TOEIC 550 2010 ETS Cisco CCNA 2010 VNPRO Training Center Cisco CCNP 2015 VNPRO Training Center Microsoft MCSE Certificate 2010 Microsoft Linux LPI 2 2009 VNLAMP Training Center VMWare VCP 2015 Robusta NetApp Training Course 2015 NetApp HP Storage Training Course 2016 HP Viet Nam Address 1024 Le Van Luong District 7 HCMC Mobile Phone 0909.63.8018 Email lamqv86@gmail.com Gender Male Date of birth July 20th 1988 Single Place of birth Ben Tre QUACH VAN LAM System Engineer lamqv86@gmail.com lamqv1986 0909.63.8018 EXPERIENCE System Engineer Sao Bac Dau Service Technology J.S.C 7/2015 Present Responsibilities Planning and deployment IT Project for customers Providing technical support to customers Researching & development IT solutions System investigation & diagnostic testing Achievement Successful in planning and implementation of many IT Projects as principal engineer.",{"entities":[[22,30,"EDUCATION"],[34,63,"MAJOR"],[69,103,"ORGANIZATION"],[109,125,"ORGANIZATION"],[161,182,"ORGANIZATION"],[199,220,"ORGANIZATION"],[231,235,"SKILL"],[263,268,"SKILL"],[280,302,"ORGANIZATION"],[303,309,"SKILL"],[310,313,"SKILL"],[319,333,"SKILL"],[355,372,"SKILL"],[414,447,"ADDRESS"],[505,509,"GENDER"],[524,538,"DATE_BIRTH"],[539,545,"MARIAGE_STATUS"],[561,568,"LOCATION"],[569,582,"PERSON_NAME"],[583,598,"JOB_TITLE"],[651,666,"JOB_TITLE"],[667,703,"ORGANIZATION"],[736,759,"SKILL"],[795,825,"SKILL"],[826,851,"SKILL"],[865,898,"SKILL"],[899,906,"SKILL"],[933,960,"SKILL"]]}]]}