{"classes":["PERSON_NAME","ADDRESS","EDUCATION","GPA","SKILL","EXPERIENCE_LEVEL","JOB_TITLE","DATE_BIRTH","MAJOR","MARIAGE_STATUS","ORGANIZATION","GENDER","LOCATION"],"annotations":[["Page 1 of 3 RESUME NGUYEN SON LINH PERSONAL INFORMATION DOB 1979 Address 257/7 Pham Van Bach Tan Binh District HCMC Vietnam Mobile +84 0908188165 Email linh_nguyenson@yahoo.com Skype sonlinhnguyen CAREER OBJECTIVES Software Development Manager Presales EMPLOYMENT HISTORY February 2009 Current Presales/Consultant/ Software Manager HiPT Vietnam Manage Software Department Provide technical proposal and Presentation for Potential customers Working with international partners to provide solution for customer i.e. GTone Atex IBM Microsoft Oracle.",{"entities":[[19,34,"PERSON_NAME"],[60,64,"DATE_BIRTH"],[73,123,"ADDRESS"],[215,252,"JOB_TITLE"],[294,331,"JOB_TITLE"],[332,344,"ORGANIZATION"],[345,371,"SKILL"],[372,398,"SKILL"],[403,415,"SKILL"],[514,519,"ORGANIZATION"],[520,524,"ORGANIZATION"],[525,528,"ORGANIZATION"],[529,538,"ORGANIZATION"],[539,545,"ORGANIZATION"]]}]]}